

Roderick Moise

Designer & Developer

W: www.rmoise.com Github: /rmoise

Linkedin: /roderickmoise

E: roderickfmoise@gmail.com

A: Berlin, Germany

Profile

From the vibrant streets of Brooklyn to Berlin's modern design scene, my career blends a rich background in NYC's ad agencies with a passion for Bauhaus-inspired design. I recently completed a full-stack web development bootcamp at CareerFoundry, where I also built my own website. Driven by a love for coding and design, I strive to create seamless, user-focused experiences that harmonize form and function.

Experience

2023 - 2024

UI / UX Designer

KARL STORZ Berlin, Germany

- Designed landing pages and email templates for KARL STORZ with Figma, enhancing brand and engagement.
- Used Figma to design website components/templates in Opentext CMS and Salesforce. Improved online catalog UX
- · Conducted competitor research and user journey mapping, offering insights to inform product development and design decisions for the online catalog.

2019 - 2022

UI / Brand Designer

Kyto Berlin, Germany

- · Created a cohesive brand strategy for Kyto, a software as a service company, and new products.
- · Created new visual identity, including marketing materials and UI for web and mobile apps, ensuring brand consistency.
- New branding, website, and mobile design boosted customer engagement, leading to Müller Medien acquisition.

2018

Product / Brand Designer

Smunch Berlin, Germany

- · Implemented a customer-centric product and brand design strategy for Smunch, a food delivery startup.
- · Conducted user research to identify pain points, enhance UX, and update visual identity for promotions.
- Achieved a 156% increase in mobile sessions and up to 2% increase in conversion rates post-launch.

Education

CareerFoundry

Fashion Institute of Technology, NY, NY

Full Stack Dev Certificate Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

BFA in Graphic Design Aug 2013 - May 2015

Skills

HTML	Tailwind
CSS	SASS/SCSS
JavaScript	Node.js
TypeScript	Express
C#	ASP.NET
React	JSON
Redux	RESTful
AngularMaterial	Postman
Bootstrap	PostgreSQL

MongoDB	TDD
AWS	Opentext CMS
Firestore	Salesforce CRN
Heroku	uı/ux
Netlify	Brand Identity
Git	Visual Design
React Native	Adobe CC
Expo	Figma
PWA	Prototyping

User Research Persona Usability Testina **User Mapping**



Roderick Moise

Designer & Developer

W: www.rmoise.com

E: roderickfmoise@gmail.com

Github: /rmoise

Linkedin: /roderickmoise

A: Berlin, Germany

Projects

2023

Document Management App

Personal Project

- · Developed a React and ASP.NET Core document management app with upload, preview, sharing, using PostgreSQL and Azure Blob Storage.
- · Added secure authentication and responsive design for all devices.
- Deployed on Azure, including user guides for easy adoption.

2023

Meet App

CareerFoundry

- Created a cohesive brand strategy for Kyto, a software as a service company, and new products.
- · Created new visual identity, including marketing materials and UI for web and mobile apps, ensuring brand consistency.
- · New branding, website, and mobile design boosted customer engagement, leading to Müller Medien acquisition.

2022

myFlix

CareerFoundry

- Created a non-relational movie database (MongoDB) and built a REST API with Node.JS and Express.
- · Tested the API endpoints with Postman, wrote clean and concise documentation, deployed the API with Heroku.
- · Designed and developed two single-page, responsive frontend applications using React and Angular.

Language

English: Native

German: Beginner

Haitian Creole: Intermediate